In this video we're gonna continue our discussion on self-type, by talking about
在这段视频中，我们将继续讨论自我类型，通过讨论
the type-level operations that are available on self-type. And this will help
Self-type上可用的类型级操作。这会有帮助的
to clarify what self-type actually is, and it's role in the type system. Let's begin
阐明自我类型到底是什么，以及它在类型系统中的作用。我们开始吧
by thinking about the example that we discussed last time and if you've
想一想我们上次讨论的例子，如果你已经
forgotten what that is, let me just write it down quickly. We had a class called
忘了那是什么了，让我快点写下来。我们有个班级叫
count, and count had one. Field an integer I that was initialized to zero and it had
伯爵，伯爵有一个。字段是一个初始化为零的整数i，它具有
one method called INC that returned something itself type and all it did was
一个名为Inc的方法返回本身类型的内容，它所做的一切是
to increment the counter field and return the self-objects. And I've probably made
若要递增计数器字段并返回自身对象，请执行以下操作。我可能已经做了
some syntax errors here but that's not really important. That's basic code for
这里有一些语法错误，但这并不重要。这是的基本代码
the CAL class. And the question is what can be the dynamic type of the object
CAL课程。问题是什么可以是对象的动态类型
that's actually returned by INC. And the answer here is it could be whatever is the
实际上是由Inc.退还的。这里的答案是，它可能是
type of this self-object. Whatever is the dynamic type of the self-object. And if we
此自我对象的类型。自我客体的动态类型是什么。如果我们
think about a big program where there is multiple classes that inherit from count.
想想一个大程序，其中有多个类继承自Count。
Then the answer is that INC could return count. Or any subclass of count. So it's
那么答案就是Inc可以返回Count。或Count的任何子类。所以这就是
going to return something that's at least, at most count, and, but it could return
返回一些至少最重要的东西，但是它可能会返回
something more specific. The dynamic type, could be something more specific, it
一些更具体的东西。动态类型，可以是更具体的，它
could be a sub classic count, or a sub class of a sub class of count. Anything
可以是子经典计数，也可以是计数的子类的子类。什么都行
that inherits directly or indirectly from count is a possibility. So what's the
直接或间接从Count继承的是一种可能性。那么是什么原因呢？
general case? Well, let's think about a class c. And in this class C, there's some
一般情况下呢？好，让我们来考虑一个c类。在这个c类中，有一些
expression buried somewhere inside of it that has the type self-type. It doesn't
埋藏在其内部某处、类型为Self类型的表达式。它不会
really matter how that expression got the type, self-type or what it is. Let's just
很重要的一点是，这个表达式是如何获得类型、自我类型或者是什么类型的。我们就这样吧
say that it has that type somehow. Well, what are the possible dynamic types of the
不知怎么的说它就是那种类型。那么，可能的动态类型是什么呢？
expression e. And from our discussion on the previous slide, it seems clear the
表达式e。从我们对上一张幻灯片的讨论中，似乎很清楚
dynamic type of e, when you run e, you're going to get back something that's a
动态类型的e，当你运行e时，你会得到一个
subtype of the class c, the enclosing class in which the self-type appears. And
类c的子类型，即自我类型出现在其中的封闭类。和
that's interestin g because it shows us that the, the meaning of self-type
这很有趣，因为它向我们展示了自我类型的意义
actually depends on the context. So, what this self-type means, this self-type means
实际上取决于上下文。所以，这种自我类型的意思是，这种自我类型的意思是
a subtype of the class C. If I'd written self-type in a class D, in the de,
类C的子类型。如果我在D类中写自类型，
somewhere in the definition of class D, there it would mean a subtype of the class
在类D的定义中的某个位置，它将表示类的子类型
D. And so to remind ourselves, what class we're talking about, what enclosing class
提醒我们自己，我们谈论的是什么类，包围的是什么类
we're talking about, we're gonna subscript occurrences of self-type with a class
我们正在讨论的是，我们将用一个类将自我类型的出现放在下标中
name. So self-types of c here is going to refer to a syntactic occurrence of the
名字。所以这里的c的自我类型指的是
keyword self-type in the body of the class c. And this also suggests a very simple
关键字self-type在类c的主体中。这也暗示了一个非常简单的
typing rule. And really the first useful fact about self-type, which is that
键入规则。关于自我类型，第一个有用的事实是
self-types of c is a sub type of c. And this is really a key idea here that a
自我类型的c是c的一个子类型，这是一个非常关键的概念
self-typing class C is some sub-type of the class C, because it also helps
自键入类C是类C的某个子类型，因为它还有助于
illustrate what self-type really is. The best way to think of an occurrence of
说明自我类型到底是什么。最好的方式来想一件事情的发生
self-type is that it's a type variable that ranges over all the sub-classes of
Self-type是一个类型变量，其范围遍及的所有子类
the class in which it appears. So self-types of C you should think of as a
它出现的班级。所以C语言的自我类型应该被认为是一种
type variable, it's something that doesn't have a fixed type, but is guaranteed to be
类型变量，它是没有固定类型，但保证是
some type founded by C, so it's gonna be only one of the class. That inherits
一些由C创建的类型，所以它将只是类中的一个。它继承了
directly or indirectly from the class c. Now that rule that self-types of c is a
直接或间接地来自类c。现在，c的自身类型是一个
sub type of the class c has an important consequence. It means that when we're
类c的子类型具有重要的结果。这意味着当我们在
doing type checking with self-type, it is always safe, always safe to replace
用自己的类型做类型检查，总是安全的，替换总是安全的
self-types of c by c. So I say, it's okay to promote any self-types of c, which
c的自我类型。所以我说，提升任何c的自我类型都是可以的，这
could be c or a sub type of c, to just say, okay, we're just going to say it's c.
可以是c，也可以是c的一个子类，也就是说，好的，我们就说它是c。
And that suggests one way to handle self-type which is just to replace all the
这就提出了一种处理自我类型的方法，那就是替换所有的
occurrences of self-type sub C by C. Now unfortunately that turns out not to be
C出现自体类型SUB C的次数现在不幸的是，事实证明并非如此
very useful. Its sound, it's correct to do that, but that's really just like not
非常有用。听起来，这样做是正确的，但那真的就像不是
having self-type at all. That's as if we went back to the example we did in the
完全没有自我类型。这就好像我们回到了我们在
last video where we started out without self-type and we found out we couldn't use
上一个视频我们开始时没有输入Self-type，但是我们发现我们不能使用
inheritance in the way we expected. So to do better than just throwing all the
以我们预期的方式继承遗产。所以要做得更好，而不是仅仅把所有的
self-types away, we need to incorporate self-type into the type system. And the
离开自我类型，我们需要将自我类型纳入类型体系。以及
way we're going to do that is by looking at the operations that work on types in
我们要做到这一点的方法是通过查看
the type system, and there are two of them. There's the sub-type relationship
类型系统，其中有两个。这是一种子类型的关系
that we've talked about before, so when one type is a sub-type of another, and
我们以前讨论过，所以当一种类型是另一种类型的子类型时，
there's the least upper bound operation that tells us what the smallest type is
有一个最小的上界运算告诉我们最小的类型是什么
that's bigger than both of two argument types. And, all we have to do and what
这比这两种参数类型都要大。我们要做的就是
we're going to do now is extend these operations to handle the type self-type.
我们现在要做的是扩展这些操作，以处理类型为self的类型。
So let's begin with a sub-type relationship and in our definition here
那么让我们从子类型关系开始，在我们这里的定义中
we're going to use sub-types T and T', and these are just normal class names. They
我们将使用子类型T和T‘，这些只是普通的类名。他们
are class names but not self-types. So one possibility is that we have self on both
是类名，但不是自身类型。所以一种可能是我们在这两个地方都有自己
sides of. Convince yourself of this. Think of self-type again, as a variable. And we
侧面。让自己相信这一点。再把Self-type看作一个变量。而我们
can plug in, for that variable, any sub-type of C. But, just like variables in
可以为该变量插入C语言的任何子类型，但是，就像
algebra, if we plug in one particular class for an occurrence of this variable,
代数，如果我们插入一个特定的类来表示这个变量的出现，
we have to pick the same one for every occurrence of the variable. So in
我们必须为该变量的每次出现选择相同的值。所以在
particular, now if we pick some sub-class A of C, then we wind up with A. Is the sub
具体地说，现在如果我们选择C的某个子类A，那么我们得到的结果是A是子类
type of A. If we plug in A for both sides we can see if their relationship holds
A类型。如果我们两边都插入A，我们就能看到他们的关系是否成立。
similarly C is the sub type of C and for any sub type we might pick, if we bind the
类似地，C是C的子类型，对于我们可能选择的任何子类型，如果我们将
variable to that sub type we can see that this relationship will be true. Now
变量设置为该子类型，则可以看出此关系将为真。现在
another thing you might think is what if the self-type sub-C is compared with
您可能会想到的另一件事是，如果将自体型SUB-C与
self-type from another class? Say self-type sub-D. And it turns out in the
另一个班级的自我打字？说自己类型的子D。结果发现，在
cool type rules this will just never come up. The cool type rules are written in
酷的类型规则这是永远不会出现的。酷类型规则是用
such a way that we never need to compare self-types from different classes. And I
这样我们就不需要比较不同班级的自我类型了。而我
haven't shown you that, that's the case yet. But when we actually go through the
我还没给你看呢，情况就是这样。但是当我们真正经历了
type rules for self-type you'll see that is true. Now another possibility is that
自我类型的类型规则，您将看到这是真的。现在另一种可能性是
we have self-type on one side and the n a regular type on the other side. So when is
我们一面有Self-type，另一面有n-a普通型。那么什么时候是
self-types of c a type of t? Well, we're going to say if that's true if C is the
自我类型的c，a类型的t？好吧，我们要说如果这是真的，如果C是
subtype of T. And here we're using our rule that it's always safe to replace
子类型T，这里我们使用我们的规则，替换总是安全的
self-type by the class that, that index is in. So in this case C is a super-type of
由该索引所在的类自行键入。所以在这种情况下，C是超类型的
anything that self-type C could be. Clearly if C is a sub-type of T if T is at
任何可能是自我C型的东西。显然，如果C是T的子类型，如果T在
least C or possibly something higher in the class higher key, then T would be a
最小的C或可能是类中更高的键，那么T将是一个
super-type of anything that self-types of C could stand for. Another case is when we
任何自我类型的C都可以代表的超级类型。另一种情况是当我们
have a regular class name on the left hand side of the sub typing relationship and
在子类型关系的左侧有一个常规类名，并且
self-type on the right hand side. And in this case it turns out we have to say that
在右手边自己打字。在这种情况下，我们不得不说
this relationship is false. That so T is never, a regular class name is never. A
这种关系是错误的。所以T永远不是，正规的类名永远不是。一个
sub type of self-type sub C. And to see this just think about the possibilities.
子类型的自我类型的子C，要看到这一点，只需考虑一下可能性。
So where can C and T be in the type hierarchy? So, if T and C are
那么C和T可以在类型层次结构中的什么位置呢？所以，如果T和C是
unrelated. You know, if they are inherent from object and they have nothing to do
不相干的。你知道，如果它们是物体固有的，它们与
with each other. Well, than clearly T can't be a sub type of self-type sub C.
彼此之间。那么很明显T不可能是自体型SubC的子类型。
They are just two unregulated classes. So, the only way that this could
他们只是两个不受管制的班级。所以，只有这样才能
possibility work out is if they are related somehow. Now if. If T is a sub
解决问题的可能性在于它们之间是否有某种联系。现在如果。如果T是SUB
type of C well then you might think that could work out. But it turns out that we
C型，那么你可能会认为这是可行的。但事实证明，我们
can't allow it even in that case. And here's the reason why, think about a
即使在这种情况下也不能允许。这就是原因所在，想一想
hierarchy where T has some subclass, let's just say that it has a subclass A. And now
层次结构，其中T有一些子类，让我们假设它有一个子类A，现在
because self-types of C ranges over all the possible subtypes of C, we could plug
因为C的自身类型覆盖了C的所有可能的子类型，所以我们可以插入
in A here and T is not a subtype of A, they're in the wrong relationship. And so
这里的A和T不是A的子类型，他们处于错误的关系中。因此，
it doesn't work for all the possible values of subtypes of C we can't say that
它并不适用于C类型子类型的所有可能值，我们不能说
this is true we have to say that it is false. Now there is one very special case.
这是真的，我们不得不说它是假的。现在有一个非常特殊的情况。
Where one could argue that we should allow this to be true. And that is in the case
有人可能会争辩说，我们应该允许这是真的。在这种情况下，情况就是这样
where T is actually a leaf of the class hierarchy. And let me actually draw this a
其中T实际上是类层次结构的叶子。让我把这张图画成
little bit differently just to emphasize this. Let's say t hat C. Is a class up
只是为了强调这一点，有点不同。比方说，C比以前高了一级。
here and then T you know, is through some chain of inheritance relationships is a
在这里，你知道，通过一些继承关系链是一个
subtype of C. So it's not immediate but there might be other classes in between.
子类型C，所以它不是直接的，但是在两者之间可能有其他类。
Just emphasize, this isn't, doesn't, this relationship doesn't have to be immediate
我只想强调，这不是，不是，我们的关系不一定是直接的
inheritance. It could be transitive inheritance. And now if T is a leaf. Of
继承。它可以是传递性继承。现在如果T是一片叶子。的
the hierarchy. If n is the only leaf of c, if c has no other sub classes then in
层级结构。如果n是c的唯一叶，如果c没有其他子类，则在
fact T is a subtype of SELF_TYPE sub C. Because it is the unique minimal type that
事实T是SELF_TYPE SUB C的子类型，因为它是
is in the subtype hierarchy of C. But the problem is that this is extremely fragile,
在C的子类型层次结构中，但问题是这是非常脆弱的，
and doesn't work, if you modify the program. In particular, a programmer might
如果你修改程序，它就不起作用了。具体地说，程序员可能
come along, and add some class A over here that's unrelated to T, but is also a
来吧，在这里添加一些A类，它与T无关，但也是一个
subclass of C. And now this would no longer work. Because if I plug in A for
子类C，现在这将不再起作用。因为如果我把A插入到
SELF_TYPE sub C, then I see that T is not a subtype of A. Right, so, we can allow
Self_type sub C，那么我看到T不是A的子类型，所以，我们可以允许
it, at a very special K. That C had only a chain of inheritance. Not a general tree
它，在一个非常特殊的K，C只有一个继承链。不是一般的树
under it. And, that T was the least of that chain. But that is so fragile. To
在它下面。而且，T是那条链条中最小的一条。但那太脆弱了。至
future program extensions. And we, you know, if you, if you broke it by
未来的程序扩展。我们，你知道，如果你，如果你打破它
adding another class over here, all of sudden you would get type errors and
在这里添加另一个类，突然之间您会收到类型错误和
pieces of codes that had previously been typed check to work and hadn't changed at
检查以前键入的代码片段是否起作用，并且未在以下位置更改
all. It just wouldn't be a very nice language design. So, summarize, T, is
全。这不会是一个很好的语言设计。所以，总结一下，T，是
never a sub type of self-types of C. And finally if we're comparing two normal
从来不是自我类型C的子类型，最后，如果我们比较两个正常的
types with not self-type then we just use the rules that we gave before. So the
如果类型不是自类型，那么我们就只使用前面给出的规则。因此，
self-typing rules we had for normal class names haven't changed at all. And that
我们对普通类名的自我键入规则根本没有改变。那就是
covers all four cases, we can have self-type on both sides, we can have
涵盖了所有四种情况，我们可以两边都有自助式，我们可以有
self-type just on the left side or just on the right side, and finally we can have a
在左边或右边自己打字，最后我们可以有一个
subtyping relationship with no self-type at all.
完全没有自身类型的子类型关系。